Talk to him on the phone
and go on a date
at some fancy places
What's this?
I did some digging
about Shin Yoo-il
Keep every detail
in mind, okay?
You know, "Trouble Maker"
has 700K subscribers
We'll be screwed
if we get caught
Ma'am…
What?
I'm an actor
Yeah, I know
You better be good
["Shin Yoo-il's Lover"]
Yes, that's the vibe
[Who's Actor Lee Hyesung?]
Yes, right
What do you like
the most about Yoo-il?
Well… you know
Yoo-il looks
a bit coldhearted
when he's focused
on something
I really like that face
One million views
already?
No wonder this guy
is a superstar…
[Shindecent]
Hello?
Where are you now?
I'm home
If you're not busy
come over to my place
Why should I?
It's been a while
since we dated at home
Since he's a celebrity
we usually date at home
Right
Are you not coming?
I'll be there
I'll send you
the address
Take care on your way